Guide to the Walter E. Fauntroy papers, 1941-1990 MS2070
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- General files, 1960-1990; MS2070 Series 1; 9 Linear feet
  - Clippings, Anti-crime proposals, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Clippings, Drugs, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Clippings, D.C. Court Cases, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Clippings, Marion S. Barry and Drug Charges, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Clippings, National Social Issues, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Brochure, "Organized to Build the Nation's Capital...", Circa 1970 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Brochure, "Special Report on Taxes", 1982 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Brochure, "Now Is the Time!", 1988 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Brochure, "Your Voice and Vote on Capital Hill", Circa 1990 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Flyer, Bicentennial Salute to the Ministry, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Flyer, King Teach-ins, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Flyer. Town Meeting on Social Security, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Flyer, Seminar on Drug Information and Prevention, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Flyer, Town Meeting on Federal Employee Health Benefits, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Flyer, Riverside Baptist Church, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Flyer, Health Care Symposium for Older Americans, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Flyer, Town Meeting on Employment, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Flyer, Spring Conference On Social Justice, the Church, and Africa and the Diaspora, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Flyer, Town Meeting on Homelessness: The Proposed Anacostia Shelter, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Flyer, Town Meeting on Drugs, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Flyer, Ossie Davis, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Flyer, Appropriation Bill for Fiscal Year 1989, 1988 October 12 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Invitation, Howard University Honorary Degrees, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Invitation, Open House for Walter E. Fauntroy, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Invitation, National Conference on Nonprofit Housing Organizations, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Invitation, Ebon Meritorious Award Ceremony, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Invitation, Birthday Celebration for Walter E. Fauntroy, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Invitation, Reception for Walter E. Fauntroy at the National Democratic Club, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Invitation, "Holiday Warm-Up", 1977 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Invitation and Ticket, Mardi Gras Masquerade Birthday Ball, 1979 February 16 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Invitation, "A Valentine Gala", 47th Birthday Party for Walter E. Fauntroy, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Invitation, Reception for Walter E. Fauntroy on his 10th Congressional Anniversary, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Invitation, Tribute Prayer Breakfast, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Invitation, "A Decade of Commitment", 1981 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Invitation, "Disco of the Decade", 1981 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Invitation, Tribute Dinner, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Invitation, Congressional Receptions for Walter E. Fauntroy, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Invitation, Holiday Reception, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Invitation, 49th Birthday Celebration for Walter E. Fauntroy, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Invitation, Reception in Honor of Small Business Week, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Invitation, Evening with Walter E. Fauntroy, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Invitation, Halloween Gala Costume Party, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Invitation, 51st Birthday Testimonial Breakfast and Mardi Gras Birthday Ball for Walter E. Fauntroy, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Invitation, Samuel C. Jackson Distinguished Citizen's Award Ceremony on Civic Night, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Invitation, 52nd Birthday Buffet for Walter E. Fauntroy, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Invitation, Reception for Walter E. Fauntroy, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Invitation, U.S. Sweetener Producers Group Reception, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Invitation, The Independence Thursday Luncheon Alumni, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Invitation, "International Fete", 1985 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Invitation, 8th Annual Democratic Gala Dinner, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Invitation, Annual Holiday Party, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Invitation, "A Day Of Reunion", 25th Anniversary of Public Service by Walter E. Fauntroy, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Invitation, More in `86 Reception, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Invitation, Reception for Martin Luther King, III, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Invitation, 25th Anniversary Alumni Association of the D.C. Youth Chorale, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Invitation, National Council of Savings Institutions, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Invitation, Kappa Alpha Psi Celebrity Auction and Soul Food Feast, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Invitation, "An International Affair", 1986 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Invitation, "54th Birthday Celebration for Walter E. Fauntroy", 1987 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Invitation, "Third Annual International Affair", 1987 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Invitation and Tickets, "A Day of Celebration", 1988 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Invitation, Black History Trail Dedication Program, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Invitation, Re-election Fundraiser, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Invitation, "Man of the Hour" Tribute to Water E. Fauntroy, undated (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Program, Rawle A. Yearwood Men's Day Dinner, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Program, D.C. Federation of Civic Associations, Inc. Awards Dinner, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Program, Howard University Trustees Dinner, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Program, Groundbreaking Ceremonies for Foster House, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Program, Harold McCully Conference, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Program, Funeral Service for Mrs. Alberta Christine Williams King [mother of Martin Luther King, Jr.], 1974 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Program, The National Black Deputy U.S. Marshal's Organization, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Program, 1st Annual Ken-King Dinner, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Program, Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. Commemorative Services, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Program, "The Continuity of Building Together" 49th Birthday Celebration for Walter E. Fauntroy, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Program, A Prayer Breakfast Honoring Walter E. Fauntroy, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Program, Black History Month, Youngstown State University, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Program, Conference of Minority Public Administrators, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Program, King Week, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Program, Salute to the Honorable Walter E. Fauntroy, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Program, Takoma Park Commemoration of Rev. Martin Luther King, Jr., 1984 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Program, Capitol Hill Reception In Honor of NACW, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Program, "Humanitarian of the Year", Touchdown Club of Washington, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Program Health Care Benefits Symposium For Older Americans, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Program, The Eleanor Roosevelt Centennial Observance, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Program, Town Meeting, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Program, 50th Anniversary Banquet of First Baptist Church of Paschall, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Program, Jewish National Fund Tree of Life Award, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Program, Senior Citizens Advisory Committee, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Program, Town Meeting on drugs, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Program, Foster Parents Christmas Reception, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Program, Zion Union Baptist Church, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Program, "A Day of Reunion", 25th Anniversary of Public Service by Walter E. Fauntroy, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Program, Prayer Breakfast, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Program, First Anniversary of the Metro Chronicle Publishers, Inc., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Program, "Shape-Up for D.C. Statehood", 1988 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Program, "Color Me Beautiful, Color Me Black", 1987 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Program, Dedication of T.S. Ledbetter Memorial Library, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Program, Annual Kennedy-King Dinner, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Program, Inauguration of Dr. Rafael Leon Cortada as President of the University of the District of Columbia, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Program, Jewels of Ann Private Day School Luncheon and Children's Fashion Show, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Program, U.S. House of Representatives Page Program, End of Year Departure Ceremony, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Program, D.C. Citizens for Federal Protection, undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Meeting Files, "To Fulfill These Rights", White House Conference, 1966 March 06 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Meeting Files, "To Fulfill These Rights", White House Conference, 1966 March 06 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Meeting Files, Walter Reed Tour and Meeting, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Meeting Files, Proceedings of North American Region Planning Committee for the 6th Pan African Congress, 1973 May 11-13 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Meeting Files, Democratic National Conference on Party Organization and Policy, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Meeting Files, Anglo-American Conference on Africa, 1978 July 01-05 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Meeting Files, Agenda for 50th Birthday Celebration, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Meeting Files, National Black Caucus of State Legislators Conference, 1984 November 28-December 02 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Meeting Files, United Black Fund Workshop, 1988 June 17 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Thomas Curen, 1964 September 22 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, William Oliver, 1965 February 18 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Tennyson Chevrolet, 1965 February 24 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, The Washington Star, 1965 May 18 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, WWD.C. Editorial, 1968 February 27 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Marjorie Lawson, 1968 June 14 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Roland Williams, 1968 August 22 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, John Conyers, Jr., 1970 April 13 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Tom Keyser, 1971 March 03 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Jean Cahn, 1971 April 01 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Staff of Marion Barry Jr., 1971 April 05 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Goding Elementary School, 1971 April 20 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Daniels Harley, 1971 April 20 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Doug Patton, 1971 April 27 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, National Black Political Convention, 1972 February 16 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Hugh Scott, 1972 May 22 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Clyde Cox, 1972 June 01 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Bob Tyson, 1972 November 09 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, National Urban League, Inc., 1973-1983 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Andrew Young, 1973 August 03 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, Emma Mimms, 1973 May 04 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, Carl Albert, 1973 May 04 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, Carolyn Walker, 1974 March 19 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, John Paxton, 1974 June 10 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, Patricia Wells, 1976 March 17 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, Black College & All American Football Classic, 1976 April 25-May 05 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, Robert Bernstein, 1976 August 26 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, Leaford Williams, 1976 November 11 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, Memorandum to Staff, 1980 December 15 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, Carl Ellison, 1981 February 27 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, Williams Chaney, 1981 March 06 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, Committee on Small Business, 1981 March 12 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, Petition Regan's Budget Proposal, 1981 March 30 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, Clarence Dember, 1981 June 06 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, Harold Washington, 1981 July 23 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, Patricia Dunson, 1981 October 28 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, Council of Churches of Greater Washington, 1981 September 04 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, Antonell Aikens, 1982 October 29 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, Civil Aeronautics Board, 1982 December 08 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence, Tom Campell and Milton Morris, 1983 February 23 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, Joseph Madison, 1983 March 15 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence, Gracia Hillman, 1983 April 07 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence, Attorney General William Smith, 1983 April 28-July 19 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence, Kenneth Duffian, OIC, 1983 May 19 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence, Frank Wolf, 1983 June 24 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence, Mayor Tom Bradley, 1983 June 27 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence, Charles Rangel, 1983 August 05 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence, Prudence Parks, 1983 September 12 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence, Walter Mondel, 1983 October 19 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence, Presidential Classroom for Young Americans, 1983 November 19 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence, Cherry Blossom Princess Escort, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence, Television and Radio Appearances, 1983-1987 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence, Children's Hospital National Medical Center, 1984 October 10 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence, Christopher Gomes, 1985 February 10 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence, Suitland Pkwy Overlook Tenants Assoc., 1985 February 03 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence, African National Congress, 1985 December 10 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence, Marion Barry- Job Training Partnership Act Proposal, 1986 April 25 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence, Reardon, Texas-Billy Graham Crusade, 1986 June 13 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence, Avery Post and Yvonne Delk, 1986 June 19 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence, Dan Rostenkowski, 1986 August 07 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence, Edward Thomas, 1986 September 25 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence, Re-elections Congratulatory Letters, 1986 September 11 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence, Peter McPherson, 1986 December 01 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence, Nomination of Charles Rangel, 1987 January 06 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence, Oswald Bronson, 1987 May 15 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence, Kelly and Chappell Fauntroy, 1987 June 09 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence, Advisory Neighborhood Commissioner, 1987 September 22 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Correspondence, John Whithead, 1987 October 25 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Correspondence, Hall Bonney, 1987 October 27 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Correspondence, David Lisher, 1987 December 12 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Correspondence, Ritchie Family Reunion, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Correspondence, Leroy Brown, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Jack S. Brook, 1988 January 05 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Snooper, 1988 January 13 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Jack Cooke, 1988 January 27 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Walter Fauntroy, 1988 February 03 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Ophelia Pinkard, 1988 February 10 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Betty Coleman, 1988 February 19 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Delois MCNeaI, 1988 March 16 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Claude Leniant, 1988 March 17 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, YMCA, 1988 March 22 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Decatur Trotter, 1988 March 23 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Frank Annunzio, 1988 March 24 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Nadine Winter, 1988 April 06 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Bryon Collins and Samuel Harvey, 1988 April 11 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Rick Swartz, 1988 April 12 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Constance Homer, 1988 April 14 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Geraldine Linder, 1988 April 14 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Mireille Kanda and Sheryl Chapman, 1988 April 14 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, O.C. Comer, 1988 May 04 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Delores Tuker, 1988 May 06 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, Marion Barry, 1989 January 09-May 24 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, Kent Cushenberry, 1988 June 06 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, William Gray, 1988 June 16 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, George Lawrence, 1988 June 20 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, Mrs. Bathrus Williams, 1988 August 18 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, Jillian Freeman (for Michael Jackson), 1988 September 13 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, Georgetown University, 1989 February 22 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, George Bush, 1989 March 03 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, Parkmont School, 1989 May 15 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, Kappa Alpha Psi Fraternity, Inc., 1988 May 25 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, William Clay, 1989 June 22 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, George Mitchell, 1989 June 26 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, The Washington Post, 1989 July 14 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, Andrew B. Stephenson, 1989 July 20 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, Frank, 1989 September 06 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, Housing Action Coalition, 1989 September 11 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, Robert Torricelli, 1989 September 13 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, Oswaldo Filho, 1989 September 26 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, Karen Johnson, 1989 October 02 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence, Dick Gregory, 1989 October 19 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, Lynn Brantley, 1989 October 20 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence, Michael Levinson, 1989 November 14 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence, Elias Burnett, 1989 November 16 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence, Embassy of Japan, 1989 November 17 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence, Rosa Parks Birthday Tribute, 1989 November 21 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence, Legislative Affairs, 1989 November 29-1990 February 20 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence, Juanita Askew, 1990 February 13 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence, Shaw Junior High School, 1990 March 14 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence, Jill Long, 1990 March 26 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence, Jack Brooks, 1990 April 20 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence, Barbara Bush, 1990 April 30 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence, Walter Scheiber, 1990 May 08 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence, Walter Ridley, 1990 June (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence, Constituent, undated (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence, John F. Ken Telegram, undated (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence, Mike Kinsbury (nephew), undated (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence, James Wilson, undated (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Gifts: Program, "A Service for Installing a Pastor", 1952 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Gifts: Book, "Ending Hunger: An Idea Whose Time Has Come", 1988 September 06 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Award, YMCA, 1962 January 30 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Award, 100 Ministers of Washington, 1974 April 29 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Award, District of Columbia Statehood Award, 1983 May 21 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Award, Ebony Magazines "100 Most Influential Black Americans, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Certificate, Membership to Pi Gamma Mu Honor Society, 1959 July 01 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Certificate, Appointment to Mayor's Econ. Development Committee, 1969 February 26 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Certificate, Appreciation in Support of Public Education, 1986 April 30 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Certificate, Who' Who in Society, 1986 May 15 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Certificate, Appreciation from the American Lung Association, 1989 July 05 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Certificate, Association for Supervision & Curriculum Development Membership, 1989 August 30 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Honor, Washington D.C. Community Education Association Lifetime Membership, 1988 November 19 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Honor, Downtown Jaycees of D.C. Membership, undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Memorabilia: Baseball Glove, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Memorabilia: Transit Pass, Capital Transit Co. $1.25, Circa 1941 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Memorabilia: Class Notes, 1952-1957 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Memorabilia: Class Notes, Church History, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Memorabilia: Student Report, "The Dynamics of Racial Segregation in American Churches", 1957 January 11 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Memorabilia: Student Report, "Psychological Foundations of Personality", 1957 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Memorabilia: Student Report, "Factors Contributing to the Successful Operation of 23 Liquor Outlets in the 19th Ward, New Haven", 1958 February 01 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Memorabilia: Christmas Card, Circa 1978 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Memorabilia: Cassette Tapes, "Celebration of Joy" (3), 1987 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Memorabilia: Trade Cards, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Memorabilia: Pins, Improved Benevolent Protective Order of Elks of the World (I.B.P.O.E.W), undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Newsletters, The Redeemer, Vol. IV No. 2, 1964 December 12 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters, Congressional, Vol. 2 No. 1, Spring, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Newsletters, WEF Congressional Newsletter, 1974-1990 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters, D.C. Democratic Newsletter, 1977 June (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters, The Capital Voice, 97th Congress, 2nd Session, 1982 May (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters, The Black Worker, 1987 July (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Newsletters, Focus, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Newsletters, Advisory Neighborhood Commission and Civic Association, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Newsletters, Fauntroy Staff Newsletter, 1989 April 08 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Negatives, 1989 December 06 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Photographs, Fauntroy and Untified Persons, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Photographs, Fauntroy (portrait), undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Photographs, Martin Luther King Jr., undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Photographs, Church, undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Photographs, Untified, 1960-1969 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Photographs, with Lyndon B. Johnson in Academia Dress, 1960-1969 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Photographs, with Robert Kennedy (includes correspondence) [photograph at Dunbar Pool taken September 11, 1963], 1963-Circa 1968 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Photographs, Martin Luther King Jr. Rally-SCLC, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Photographs, White House Conference with Spike McKissck, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Photographs, Walter Reed Army Medical Center, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Photographs, National Symphony Orchestra at the Embassy of Turkey, 1972 December 02 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Photographs, Congressional Baseball Game, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Photographs, with U.S. Military Academy Nominee, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Photograph Proof Sheet, Housing Now March, 1989 October 12 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Photographs, with Derek Horton, Winner of the 1989 Award for Creative Merit, 1989 June 29 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Slides, Urban Redevelopment-Shaw 14th Street, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    General
    This folder is currently empty.
  - Slides, Bicentennial Presentation, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - News Releases, Democratic National Committee, 1972 June 28 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - News Releases, NAACP, 1974 July 03-1984 October 10 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - News Releases, Hearing on Fitness, 1976 June 22 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - News Releases, New Press Secretary, 1976 November 30 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - News Releases, Budget Cuts, 1979 July 09 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - News Releases, Resignation of Andrew Young, 1979 August 19 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - News Releases, Maryland Legislators, 1980 January 30 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - News Releases, Endorsing Senator Edward Kennedy, 1980 February 01 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - News Releases, Washington Exhibit, 1980 March 14 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - News Releases, Constituent Services, 1980 April 24 (Box 15, Folder 10)